Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/munafkapadia (LinkedIn) munafkapadia.com (Personal) thebohrikitchen.com (Company)

Top Skills

Google Adwords
Online Advertising
Online Marketing

Languages

Hindi English Gujarati

Honors-Awards Forbes 30 Under 30

TedX Speaker, SP Jain School of Management Winner, Grilled TV Reality Show IIT Bombay Speaker

Top 50 Young Marketer Award

Publications

Major Potential for Minority Cuisines
How this Kitchen became a favourite
haunt of Bollywood Celebs
Deep Thoughts on Deep Discounting
Challenges of setting up The Bohri
Kitchen

Divided by Politics, United by food

Munaf Kapadia

The Guy Who Quit Google to Sell Samosas Mumbai

Summary

Worked 4 years as an Account Strategist at Google India and 5 years as Founder and CEO of Bohri Kitchen Pvt Ltd. As CEO, I have recruited and led a team of 40+ employees, built senior leadership across core functions and executed a cohesive branding and marketing strategy which led to an annual outlook of INR 4.5 crores (2019), generated over INR 7 crores worth of organic press and put me on the cover of the Forbes India 30 Under 30 Edition (2017). I have also been commissioned by Harper Collins to write a book 'The Guy Who Quit Google to Sell Samosas' (slated for release end of 2020).

Experience

The Bohri Kitchen
Founder & CEO
August 2015 - Present (5 years 1 month)
Mumbai Area, India

TBK is an award winning, digital first food venture recognised for successfully capturing pan-india mindshare for a niche cuisine

- Scaled Distribution: Set up 4 Cloud Kitchens and a QSR
- 100% Sales Growth YoY: From INR 25L to 4.5 Crs in 4 years
- Team Building & Delegation : Recruited & led 40+ employees
- INR 7 Crs+ Organic Press : Including International & Indian Media spanning the NY Mag, BBC, FT London, TOI, The Hindu, Mint, Economic Times etc.
- Setup City-Wide Supply Chain : Streamlined operations and production by identifying the right food partners

- Celebrity Clientele : Bollywood, government leadership, consulates & corporates
- Benchmark in Dining Experiences : First in its category The Bohri Kitchen Home Dining Experience

Google

Account Strategist March 2011 - August 2015 (4 years 6 months) Mumbai Area, India

- Consulted the top 10 BFSI advertisers & reported to the former Head of Google India
- Doubled annual sales from \$5m to \$10m
- Promoted twice & founded company wide initiatives (NGO Consultants & Idea Factory)

"Munaf, you think like Larry Page" - Nikesh Arora (Former Chief Business Officer, Google)

Education

SVKM's Narsee Monjee Institute of Management Studies (NMIMS) MBA, Marketing · (2009 - 2011)

Narsee Monjee College of Commerce and Economics Bachelor of Business Administration - BBA, Marketing · (2006 - 2009)

H.R. College of Commerce and Economics HSC, Business/Commerce, General · (2004 - 2006)

The Cathedral and John Connon School ICSE · (1994 - 2004)